Han Sol Lee

Full-Stack Web Developer

Solly0702@gmail.com | | 206.409.6713 | | Seattle, WA

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

Web Developer proficient in Python with Django, MEAN, and Ruby on Rails stack with the ability to develop web applications from concept to implementation. Received full stack web development training. Acquired strong fundamental knowledge of web application with database including both SQL and NoSQL. Experienced with user research, testing and deployment. Strong attention to details, with ability to swiftly adapt and committed to meeting the needs. Excellent communicator and team player.

Professional Skills

- Coding Languages: JavaScript, Python, Ruby
- Front-End Development: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, ECMA-Script6, jQuery, Ajax
- Database: MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Frameworks & Libraries: Angular.js React.js, Node.js, Express, Socket.io, Ruby on Rails, Django, Flask, Twitter Bootstrap, Google API, Lodash
- Development Tools: Submile-text, Atom, Bash-Terminal, Vim, Git/Github, Wireframe, ERD, NPM, Bower, RESTful Architecture, Object-Oriented Programing, Nginx
- Languages: English, Korean

EDUCATION

Coding Dojo | Bellevue, WA | April 2016

• Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

Embry Riddle Aeronautical University | Seattle, WA | September 2013

Bachelor of Science in Aeronautics, Minor in Management

GPA: 3.85

- Graduated magna cum laude from Embry Riddle Aeronautical University, 2013
- Awarded the Future Alumni Scholarship twice and the Eagle-Vision Leader Award at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University, 2012-2013
- Dean's List recipient nine times at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University, 2011-2013

South Seattle Community College | Seattle, WA | June 2010

Associated of Applied Science in Aeronautical Technology

GPA: 3.49

- Honor Roll/Dean's List six times for outstanding academic achievement at South Seattle Community College, 2008-2009
- Awarded the International Programs Academic Scholarship at South Seattle Community College, 2009

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Dojopool | MEAN

Web application where users register and login to upload schedules for carpools and requests for joining carpools. Users can accept requests from each other. Utilized Google Maps API to check drivers' starting, ending and meeting locations for carpools.

Technologies Used: JavaScript, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, Angular, Google API, Node.js, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, and CSS3.

Professional Website | MEAN

Web application that describes my professional experience and skills. Implements self-taught knowledge of React with Redux architecture.

Technologies Used: JavaScript, Express is, Node is, React, Twitter Bootstrap for React, HTML5, and CSS3.

Han Sol Lee

Full-Stack Web Developer

Solly0702@gmail.com | | 206.409.6713 | | Seattle, WA

Secret Board | Ruby on Rails

Web application where users can write their secrets and other users can share the secrets and mark them as like or unlike. Built with Test Driven Development methodology.

Technologies Used: Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, bcrypt, simple_form, capybara, rspec-rails

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

QA Software Test Engineer | Bellevue, WA | September 2014 – December 2015

Samsung Electronics America, contracted with J&D Solutions

- Executed and created test plans and clear, concise test scripts for new products or enhancements to existing products
- Defined moderate-level test scenarios and variation in accordance with test scripts provided by manufactures and mobile carriers
- Performed appropriate testing, submitted errors and issues to Research & Development for correction, and retested to ensure effectiveness of resolutions
- Collected various types of failure logs by requests from Research & Development
- Reported test results and statuses as appropriate with applicable work forms
- Coordinated and performed basic testing projects from initiation to delivery and ensured that projects were completed on schedule
- Ensured software solutions met customer requirements for usability and functionality
- Assisted with education and training of other employees on proper software enhancements and conveying corrections

Aeronautical Mechanic | Kirkland, WA | January 2014 – September 2014

Nabtesco Aerospace, Inc.

- Built and repaired hydraulic, electric, and hydroelectric units for aircrafts, such as speed brake hydraulic actuators and hydraulic flap actuators for Cessna aircrafts, yaw damper servo for Boeing 757 and 767, Multi-Function Spoiler Actuator for Embraer 170, and rack and panel for Boeing 787
- Completed troubleshooting, overhauling, repairing, servicing, and manufacturing on units with applicable work forms in accordance with Component Maintenance Manual, manufacturers' manuals and engineering orders
- Performed hydraulic and electric testing to assure that units met FAA requirements, safety, and airworthiness
- Reported electrical, hydraulic and electro-hydraulic test results and statuses of units to Engineering Department for enhancement

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATIONS

- Airport Management Certificate, 2013
- Information Assurance (National Security Agency) Certificate, 2013
- General Radiotelephone Operator License with Radar Endorsement, 2013
- FAA Airframe and Powerplant Airman Certificate, 2010